Izzy: Sorry I’m late.
Ben: No problem.
Are you OK?
Izzy: Yeah, I’m fine.
Congratulations, Ben.
Your show was great.
I’m sorry I left like that.
Ben: That’s OK.
Izzy: No, it’s not OK.
I don’t know why I did that.
Ben: Don’t worry.
I understand.
Andre isn’t easy sometimes.
Is that why you left the school?
Izzy: I didn’t really like him as a teacher, but no.
Andre wasn’t the problem.
Ben: What was the problem?
Izzy: I love taking photos, but…when I was at the school, I stopped loving it.
I thought it was what I wanted to do, but it wasn’t.
Ben: That’s too bad.
Izzy: Yeah…but it was a good decision.
I love photography again.
And now I’m in the ‘real world.’
Ben: And how is it? The real world?
Izzy: I like it.
I think I like it.
Let’s go. Where’s the restaurant?
Ben: It’s this way.
Can I see some of your photos now, please?
Izzy: Oh, I don’t take many photos these days.
Ben: Yes, you do. You take photos all the time.
Izzy: Do I?
Do I take photos all the time?
Mm? Mm? Smile, please…